Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Union Spotlight, 1956; Publication (Box 169, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.1:no.12
  - Item 2: Union Spotlight, 1957; Publication (Box 169, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.2:no.2-3,5-12
  - Item 3: Union Spotlight, 1958; Publication (Box 169, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1-3,5-9
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A practical course in electricity for apprentice classes, 1930; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
    Author: Walter E. Coburn
  - Item 2: Decision rendered by Judge Phillips in the Electrical Workers controversy, 1912; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: How it is done: read carefully., 1921; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Pre-Industrial survivals: open shoppers expose the open shop, 1929; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprinted from Feb., Mar., Apr., and May, 1929 Electrical Workers' Journal. 2 copies
  - Item 5: Propaganda rides her broom again by Smith Smithson, 1936; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprint from the Journal of Electrical Workers and Operators
  - Item 6: That job of yours, 1922; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: That job of yours, 1929; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The council on Industrial Relations for the Electrical Construction Industry - Bulletin no. 1, 1951; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The power revolution: an outline study, 1926; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
    Author: Arthur W. Calhoun
  - Item 10: Your trade union, 1948; Publication (Box 170, Folder 1)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Biography of a labor union: a chronicle of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Directory of local unions, 1943; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Employment plan of the Electrical Contracting Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: First report of the Labor-Management Planning Committee on Postwar Problems of the National Electrical Contractors Association and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1943; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Pension plans what you should know about them, Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Plain talk with the Electrical Worker, Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Preliminary report of the Labor-Management Planning Committee on Postwar Problems of the National Electrical Contractors Association and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers., 1943; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Second report of the Labor-Management Planning Committee on Postwar Problems of the National Electrical Contractors Association and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1944; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Vacations with pay: policy and practice in IBEW local unions, Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Your membership in the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1938; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Your trade union the I.B.E.W., 1943; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Your trade union the IBEW, 1947; Publication (Box 170, Folder 2)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1953 Banner Year for IBEW..., Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 39.9 million a year!, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Appraisal by the IBEW of various recommendations of article committees, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Calling all telephone workers, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Doodling that counts!!, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: IBEW ritual of procedure for use of Local Unions, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: I've been a member 50 years, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Principle of insulation, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: This is an IBEW Plant, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: $ and sense, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: 25 million a year!, 1959; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Annual wage - politics or engineering?, 1945; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
    Author: M. H. Hedges
    Notes: Reprinted from Electrical Contracting. 2 copies
  - Item 13: Brotherhood on the march, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Daniel W. Tracy...released a letter....urgently protesting the ant-union policies of the Rural Electrification Admin., 1948- 1950 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    Author: Daniel W. Tracy
  - Item 15: Local union 213 IBEW - 50 years, 1951; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1958; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1959; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Speech by Secretary of Labor Maurice J. Tobin, 1948-1950 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    Author: Maurice J. Tobin
  - Item 19: St. Louis Missouri, Electrician Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Stewardship: Social contribution of the accountant to labor-management relations, 1947; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Suggestions for union stewards and those handling grievances, 1948; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: The I.B.E.W. looks at restrictive labor laws, 1958; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: The International Executive Council of IBEW endorses the action and policy of Int'l. Pres. D.W. Tracy in opposing public ownership trend in the Electric Light and Power Ind., 1948-1950 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: The Journal of Electrical Workers and Operators - IBEW signs working agreement with REA, 1941; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: The role of trade unions in democratizing public enterprise: TVA, 1945; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: To the members of the IBEW and employees of the Consolidated Edison System TRUTH, 1936; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Your trade union the IBEW, 1945; Publication (Box 170, Folder 3)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Citizenship responsibility and political education: outline for IBEW local union registrars and local union committees on political education, Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Correspondence to Members of Congress, 1971; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
    Notes: re: Dec. issue of the Electrical Workers Journal
  - Item 3: Employees Security Fund, 1962; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Patterns for progress in aging, 1964; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Pension plans what you should know about them, Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Programme, Local 3, IBEWvisit to Jamaica, West Indies, 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Report, NECA Pension benefit trust fund, 1973; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The IBEW leads to electrifying careers, Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: This is the IBEW, 1957; Publication (Box 170, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood on the march, one union, one brotherhood we go forward together, Publication (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: IBEW handbook for conducting pre-retirement programs, 1970-1979 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Outline of study for staff members, Publication (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: St. Louis Missouri, Electrician Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 170, Folder 5)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1961; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1962; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1963; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1964; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1966; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1967; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Report on the I.B.E.W. pension benefit trust fund, 1971; Publication (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Report, NECA Pension benefit trust fund, 1968-1969 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Report, NECA Pension benefit trust fund, 1975-1976 (Box 170, Folder 6)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 50 years of service - Research and Education Dept. - IBEW, Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Analysis of severance plans in major IBEW utility companies, Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Hospital, medical, surgical plans of IBEW Survey, 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Life ins. Survey for large electric utility co., suppl., 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Survey of retirement plans in selected IBEW, 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 7)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Analysis of severance plans in major IBEW utility companies, Publication (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: In your service, 1974; Publication (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Selected reprinted articles for the IBEW Journal, 1972-1974 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Survey of retirement plans in selected IBEW, 1960; Publication (Box 170, Folder 8)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A strikeless industry, 1932; Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship in the electrical industry, Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Facts concerning municipal ownership of public utilities, particularly electric utilities, 1935; Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: How to install a local research service for electrical workers, Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Pension plans: what you should know about them, Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Research Dept.
  - Item 6: Research for action by Marion M. Hedges, 1938; Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Specimen state electrical law, 1939; Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The contribution of organized labor to a Christian social order, 1928; Publication (Box 170, Folder 9)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union Lite Newsletter, 1959-1960 (Box 171, Folder 1)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union Lite Review, 1960-1961 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-4
  - Item 2: Union Lite Review, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-2,5-12
  - Item 3: Union Lite Review, 1962-1963 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.3:no.3-7
  - Item 4: Union Lite Review, 1964-1965 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.4:no.2,4-6
  - Item 5: Union Lite Review, 1967; Publication (Box 171, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.5:no.17-1/2-31- 35
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Union Lite Review, 1964-1965 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.4:no.7-13
  - Item 2: Union Lite Review, 1965-1966 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-13, 15-17
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Western Electric Council, the IBEW and the Univ. of Wisconsin School of Workers, 1965; Publication (Box 171, Folder 4)
    Notes: Job Evaluation Institute, schedule
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Third Biennial Convention of the Electrical Workers Benefit Assoc., 1927; Publication (Box 172, Folder 1)
- International Union of Elevator Constructors, Publication (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report on negotiations for the general membership in the US, 1972; Publication (Box 172, Folder 2)
    Author: International Union of Elevator Constructors
  - Item 2: The Elevator Constructor - Candidates' Labor Record, 1968; Publication (Box 172, Folder 2)
- International Union of Elevator Constructors, Publication (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Circular letter dated Aug. 27, 1964, Publication (Box 172, Folder 3)
    Author: International Union of Elevator Constuctors
  - Item 2: Strike bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 172, Folder 3)
- Southern California Professional Engineering Association, Publication (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1961-1963 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    Author: Southern California Professional Engineering Association
- Engineering Employers' Federation, Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The SPEEA Bulletin, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    Author: Seattle Professional Engineering Employee Association (SPEEA)
  - Item 2: The SPEEA salary data, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The SPEEA Spotlite, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The SPEEA Survey, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Continuing Engineering Education Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Correspondence, 1965; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Health ins. Program, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Incentive compensation facts, 1962; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Incentive compensation facts, 1963; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Incentive compensation facts, 1964; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Incentive compensation facts, 1965; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Procedure for the avoidance of disputes - Manual Workers agreement between the Engineering Employers' Federation and the Confederation of Shipbuilding and Engineering Unions, 1976; Publication (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: SPEEAhistoryaccomplishmentsplansphilosophy, 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 5)
- SPEEA (Seattle Professional Engineering Employee Association), Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Merit raise facts (July 7, 1961), Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Salary data for engineers, 1962; Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 1 (1962)
  - Item 3: Salary data for engineers, 1963; Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 1 (1963)
  - Item 4: SPEEA Engineers Data, 1965; Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: SPEEA Engineers Data, 1966; Publication (Box 172, Folder 6)
- Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 172, Folder 7)
    Author: Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel
  - Item 2: Princeton Sociologist looks at our unions: Unions for Engineers, 1960; Publication (Box 172, Folder 7)
    Notes: Reprinted from Princeton Engineer
  - Item 3: Salary Survey, 1964-1966 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Salary Survey, 1971; Publication (Box 172, Folder 7)
- Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Exponent, 1956; Publication (Box 172, Folder 8)
    Author: Association of Professional Engineering Personnel
    Notes: vol.8:no.1-5, 7-12
  - Item 2: Exponent, 1957; Publication (Box 172, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.9:no.1-13
  - Item 3: Exponent, 1958; Publication (Box 172, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.10:no.1-8
  - Item 4: Exponent, 1959; Publication (Box 172, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.11:no.1-2
- Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Exponent, 1952; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-7
  - Item 2: Exponent, 1953; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-2, 4-7
  - Item 3: Exponent, 1955; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-9
  - Item 4: Exponent, 1958; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.10:no.5
  - Item 5: Exponent, 1959; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.11:no.3-6
  - Item 6: Exponent, 1960; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.12:no.1, 3-4
  - Item 7: Exponent, 1961; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.13:no.2-7
  - Item 8: Exponent, 1962; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.14:no.1-11
  - Item 9: Exponent, 1963; Publication (Box 172, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.15:no.1-2
- Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Exponent, 1960; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.12:no.2
  - Item 2: Exponent, 1961; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.13:no.1
  - Item 3: Exponent, 1962; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.14:no.12
  - Item 4: Exponent, 1963; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.15:no.3-8
  - Item 5: Exponent, 1964; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.16:no.1-6
  - Item 6: Exponent, 1965; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.17:no.1-7
  - Item 7: Exponent, 1966; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.18:no.1-3
  - Item 8: Exponent, 1967; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.19:no.1-2A, 5-6
  - Item 9: Exponent, 1968; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.20:no.1-2
  - Item 10: Exponent, 1969; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.21:no.1-3
  - Item 11: Exponent, 1970; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.22:no.1-2
  - Item 12: Exponent, 1971; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.23:no.1-2
  - Item 13: Exponent, 1972; Publication (Box 172, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.24:no.1
- Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 172, Folder 11)
- E.S.G. Steering Committee, Publication (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: E.S.G. Steering Committee, 1957; Publication (Box 173, Folder 1)
    Author: E.S.G. Steering Committee
    Notes: Press Release
  - Item 2: E.S.G. Steering Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Preamble, Publication (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Southern California Professional Engineering Association, Publication (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A base for union democracy, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Fay's union denies he ran it from cell, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: NLRB examiner urges clamp on engineer local, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Union charges dictator rule by officers, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Douglas and Southern California Professional Engineering Assoc., 1957; Publication (Box 173, Folder 2)
    Author: Douglass Aircraft Company, Inc.
  - Item 6: Ex-Union leader seeks to quiz fay, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Union reaffirms ouster of 2 men, 1953-1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
- Federation Reporter, Publication (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Federation Reporter, 1957; Publication (Box 173, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.3:no.2, 5 (Feb., May, 1957)
  - Item 2: Federation Reporter, 1957; Publication (Box 173, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.3, Special Issue (Mar., 1957)
  - Item 3: The Federation Story, 1956; Publication (Box 173, Folder 3)
    Author: Minneapolis Federation, Honeywell Engineers
- ESA (Engineers and Scientists of America), Publication (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: High Court urged to set safeguard in loyalty cases, 1954; Publication (Box 173, Folder 4)
    Notes: reprinted from The New York Times, Tues. Dec. 28, 1954
  - Item 2: The Engineering and Scientists of America by Engineering and Scientists of America, Jan. 1, 1954, Publication (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Why Engineers Organize by Republic Engineering Assoc., Oct. 30, 1953, Publication (Box 173, Folder 4)
- ESA (Engineers and Scientists of America), Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Engineering Associations take on a union patina, 1954; Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
    Notes: article from Business Week, Aug., 1954
  - Item 2: Engineer-scientist employee groups plan recruiting drive, set new goals, 1953; Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
    Notes: Reprint, Mar. 1953
  - Item 3: ESA Special Report, 1957-1958 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    Author: Engineers and Scientists of America
    Notes: Report no. 1-5 (Nov., 1957 - June, 1958). 2 copies
  - Item 4: Presidents report to ESA Convention, 1953; Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Engineers Unions are here, 1955; Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
    Notes: Reprinted from Consulting Engineer, Jan. 1955
  - Item 6: The Southern California Professional Engineering Association, Publication (Box 173, Folder 5)
- SPEEA (Seattle Professional Engineering Employee Association), Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1955 SPEEA pocket manual, Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
    Author: Seattle Professional Engineering Employees Association
  - Item 2: A case study: employee analysis reports, 1959; Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Salary growth of Boeing engineers, 1957; Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: SPEEA News Release -, 1961; Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: SPEEA News Release -, 1962; Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: SPEEA's negotiation questionnaire for 1959, Publication (Box 173, Folder 6)
- ESA (Engineers and Scientists of America), Publication (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Before the NLRB - docket no. 4-RC-3594. Pennsylvania Power & Light Company and Utility Engineers Assoc., Engineers and Scientists of America, 1959; Publication (Box 173, Folder 7)
    Notes: Brief on behalf of Penn. Power & Light Co.
- Strike cuts work on hydrogen bomb, Publication (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Strike cuts work on hydrogen bomb, 1952; Publication (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Strike is called off at atomic plant, 1952; Publication (Box 173, Folder 8)
- AFTE (American Federation of Technical Engineers), Publication (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 43% R. Hoe Employees receive merit hikes, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Agreement signed at Waverly Atomic Energy project, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: General Electric council meets in Philadelphia, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Independent Engineers Union Affiliates with AFTE, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Iron lung available to members and their families, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Local 153 wins increases at Chicago Park District, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: New construction wage scale established for technical engineers, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: New Local at Kankakee, Ill., 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: New local chartered at Phoenix, Ariz., 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: A brief outline of the Technical Engineers and Architects Association... of the American Federation of Technical Engineers, affiliate of American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 173, Folder 9)
    Author: American Federation of Technical Engineers
  - Item 11: Additional gains by Local 66, New York, in negotiations, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Convention programs - 31st National Conventions, 1954; Publication (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Convention programs - 30th National Conventions, 1952; Publication (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Local 241 wins NLRB election, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
- Architectural and Engineering Guild, Publication (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Monthly publication, 1937-1943 (Box 173, Folder 10)